A Guide to Arena Stage Photographs, [1950-1991]
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage Photographs
  - A Midsummer Nights Dream 1989 - 1990 (Box Box 5)
    Pamela Nyberg, Neil Maffin, Tom Hewitt, Regan Byrne, Sara Hope Franks, Bill Mondy, Christina Moore, Neil Maffin, Pamela Nyberg, Pamela Nyberg, Neil Maffin
  - The Miser 1955 (Box Box 12)
  - The Moon in the Yellow River 1962 (Box Box 6)
  - Mother Courage 1970 - 1971 (Box Box 6)
    Jane Alexander, Richard Bauer, Micheal Fairman, Donegan Smith, Ned Beatty, Frank Adu
  - The Mousetrap 1953 (Box Box 6)
    Lester Rawlins, Emily Mclaughlin, Francis Ingalls
  - Mr. Arcularis 1951 (Box Box 6)
    Lester Rawlins, Jacqueline Dudley, Mary Pray Conlin, Harry Skully, Dick O'Neil, Pernell Roberts, Warner Schreiner, Henry Oliver, Laura Worth, Orville French
  - Mummenschanz 1979 - 1980 (Box Box 6)
    Mark Olsen, Mark Thompson, Claudia Weiss
  - Mississippi Delta 1990 - 1991 (Box Box 6)
    Jonathan Wilson, Cheryl Lyn Bruce, Sybil Walker, Jacqueline Williams
  - Monteith and Rand 1983 - 1984 (Box Box 6)
    Suzanne Rand, John Monteith
  - A Month in the Country 1958 - 1959 (Box Box 6)
    Nicolas Coster, Louise Latham, Astrid Wilsrud, Philip Bosco
  - My Children, My Africa 1990 - 1991 (Box Box 6)
    Herb Downer, Robin Morse, Teagle F. Bougere
  - Moonchildren 1971 - 1972 (Box Box 6)
    Kevin Conway, Maureen Anderman, Christopher Guest, Stephen Collins, Edward Herrmann, Cara Duff-MacCormack
  - My Hearts in the Highlands 1953 (Box Box 6)
    Stanley Pitts, Clay Hall, Frank Hamilton
  - National Health 1977 (Box Box 6)
    Leonardo Cimino, Veronica Castang, Stanley Anderson, Mark Hammer, Terrence O'Hara, Paula Desmond, C.C.H. Pounder, Veronica Castang, Paula Desmond
  - Nevis Mountain Dew 1979 (Box Box 6)
    Frances Foster, Arthur French, Ethel Ayler, Graham Brown, Barbara Montgomery
  - Night Mother 1985 - 1986 (Box Box 6)
    Halo Wines, Ann Guilbert
  - Nighclub Conteta 1977 (Box Box 6)
    David Schechter, Karen Evans, Jossie deGuzman, Mark Zagaeski
  - The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail 1970 - 1971 (Box Box 6)
    Micheal Fairman, Howard Witt, Donegan Smith, Grayce Grant, Theodore Wilson, Jill Eikenberry
  - The 1940's Radio Hour 1978 - 1979 (Box Box 6)
    Sherman Lloyd, John Doolittle, Jack Hallett, Crissy Wilzak, Stephen James, Jeff Keller, Joe Grifasi, Donna Drake, Jeff Keller, Franchelle Stewart Dorn, Timothy Jerome
  - No Place to Be Somebody 1969 - 1970 (Box Box 6)
    Richard Bauer
  - Nat X 1973 (Box Box 6)
  - Nothing Sacred 1988 - 1989 (Box Box 6)
    Casey Biggs, Bob Kirsh, Bill Mondy, Petronia Paley, Clayton LeBouef, Henry Strozier, John Elko
  - Of Mice and Men 1950 (Box Box 6)
    Henry Oliver, Dorothea Jackson, Lester Rawlins, Tober Fedder, Henry Lampe, Harry Shully, Jack Carter, Forest Monroe, Stuart Smith
  - Oh What a Lovely War 1966 (Box Box 6)
  - Old Times 1985 - 1986 (Box Box 6)
    Tana Hicken, Halo Wines, Stanley Anderson
  - On the Razzle 1982 - 1983 (Box Box 6)
    Stanley Anderson, Mark Hammer, Christina Moore, Barbara Sohmers, Halo Wines, Jhon Edward Mueller, Katherine Leask, Michael Heintzman, Yeardly Smith, Kevin Donovan
  - On The Town 1988 - 1989 (Box Box 6)
    Gordon Paddison, David Marks, Paul Binotto, Jhon Scherer, Valerie Wright, Kathleen Mahony-Bennett, Adriane Lenox, Regan Byrne, Sarah Hope Franks
  - On the Way Home - Stephen Wade 1989 - 1991
    Regan Byrne, Sara Hope Franks
  - Once Around the Block (3 Short Plays) 1958 (Box Box 6)
    Marry Harrigan, Skedge Miller, Patricia Ripley, Cay Knockey, Charlie Byrd, Robert Elston, Harry Bergman
  - Once In A Lifetime 1962 (Box Box 6)
    Roy Scheider, Rene Auberjonois, Bella Jarrett
  - Once in a Lifetime 1976 (Box Box 6)
    Bella Jarrett, David Leary, Robert Prosky, Moss Hart, George S. Kaufman
  - One Flew Over the Cukoo's Nest 1972 - 1973 (Box Box 6)
    Stanley Anderson, Richard Bauer, E.L. James, Howard Witt, Gary Bayer, Terrence Currier, Garrett Saunders, Manu Tupou, Judith Long, Lane Binkley
  - One Mo Time 1980 (Box Box 6)
    Ron Wyche, Thomas E. Short, Jr., James W. Howard, Arthur Dawkins, Harold Mann, Morten Larsen, Peggy Alston, Barbara Montgomery, Lady B.J., Tom Hull
  - Othello 1963 (Box Box 6)
  - Our Town 1953 (Box Box 7)
    Anne Leslie, Marian Reardon, Frances Sternhagen, Dick O'Neill
  - Our Town 1990 - 1991 (Box Box 7)
    Robert Prosky, Christina Moore, David Aaron Baker,Jaime Sanchez, Halo Wines
  - Ourselves Alone 1987 (Box Box 7)
    Randy Danson, Christina Moore, Heather Ehlers, Christopher McHale, Robert Westenberg, Thomas Anthony Quinn
  - Pantagleize 1971 - 1972 (Box Box 7)
    Linda Geiser, Richard Bauer, Macon McCalman
  - Pantomine 1980 - 1981 (Box Box 7)
    Richard Bauer, Avery Brooks
  - Passion Play 1984 - 1985 (Box Box 7)
    Jayne Haynes, Halo Wines, Tana Hicken, Stanley Anderson, Marilyn Caskey, Ned Schmidtke
  - The Philadelphia Story 1985 - 1986 (Box Box 7)
    Henry Strozier, Heather Ehlers, John Leonard, Tom Hewitt, Casey Biggs, Laila Robins
  - A Phoenix too Frequent 1953 (Box Box 7)
    Marian Reardon
  - Pictures in the Hallway 1958 (Box Box 7)
    Tom Bosley, Alan Coates, Nicolas Coster, Clayton Corzatte, Pauline Flanagan, Margaretta Warwick, Astrid Wilsrud
  - The Piggy Bank 1985 - 1986 (Box Box 7)
    Veronica Castang, Marissa Chibas, Mark Hammer, Henry Strozier, Stanley Anderson, Robert Westenberg
  - Play, That Time, Footfalls 1976 - 1977 (Box Box 7)
  - Playboy of the West Indies 1988 - 1989 (Box Box 7)
    Mustapha Matura, Tonia Rowe, L. Peter Callender, Leon Addison Brown, Tonia Rowe, LaDonna Mabry, Faye Richie, Margo Hall, Sullivan Walker, Keith Johnson, David Toney, James Brown-Orleans
  - The Playboy of the Western World 1951 (Box Box 7)
    Henry Oliver, Marion Karczmar, Bill McGuire, Mary Pray Conlin
  - Plenty 1980 (Box Box 7)
    Timothy Jerome, Blair Brown, Jim Jenner, Terrence Currier, John Glover, Joan MacIntosh
  - The Plough and the Stars 1959 (Box Box 7)
    Alan Coates, Tom Brannum, Lyn Alstad, Jhon Dignan
  - Portrait of a Madonna 1957 (Box Box 7)
    Dorothea Hammond, Del Tenney
  - Poar Bitas 1967 (Box Box 7)
    Anna Carparelli, Richard Venture
  - The Prisoner 1957 (Box Box 7)
    Lester Rawlins, Gene Gross, Allen Joseph, Del Tenney
  - Project Immortality 1966 (Box Box 7)
    James Kennx, Lauri Peters, Jon Voight
  - A Public Prosecutor Is Sick Of It All 1973 (Box Box 7)
    Max Wright
  - Pygmalian 1990 - 1991
    Regan Byrne, Sarah Hope Franks, Richard Bauer, Charles Dumas, June Hansen, Terrence Currier, Gail Grate, Terrence Currier, Tammy Grimes, Jenifer Mendenhall
  - Pygmalion 1950 - 1951 (Box Box 7)
    Lester Rawlins, Harry Scully, Warner Shreiner, Zelda Fichandler, Henry Oliver
  - Quartermaine's Terms 1983 - 1984 (Box Box 7)
    Charles Janasz, Derek Meadle, Jack Aranson, Jackson Aranson, Henry Strozier, Lynn Milgrim, Frederica Meister, James Cahill, Stanley Anderson
  - Rain 1955 (Box Box 7)
  - Raisin 1972 - 1973 (Box Box 7)
    Ralph Carter, Jope Morton, Ernestine Jackson, Richard Sanders, Shezwae Powell, Virginia Capers
  - Real Estate 1984 - 1985 (Box Box 7)
    Stanley Anderson, Fran Brill, Jeffrey Hayenga
  - The Regard of Flight 1985 - 1986 (Box Box 7)
    M.C. O'Connor, Bill Irwin
  - The Rehearsal 1964 - 1965 (Box Box 7)
    Sara Croft, Philip Charles Mackenzie, Barbara Lester
  - Relatively Speaking 1973 - 1974 (Box Box 7)
    Sara Croft, Philip Charles Mackenzie, Barbara Lester, Paul Collins, Katherine Squire, Donald Ewer, June Hansen, Stanley Anderson
  - The Resistible Rise of Arturo 1973 - 1974 (Box Box 7)
    Richard Bauer, Wendell W. Wright Jr., Gene Minkow
  - Teibele and Her Demon, 1978-1980, folder 1 (Box box 8)
  - The Tempest, 1984-1985, folder 2 (Box box 8)
  - The Tenth Man, 1967-1968, folder 3 (Box box 8)
  - Theatre Carnival, 1953, folder 4 (Box box 8)
  - Three Men on a Horse, 1952, folder 5 (Box box 8)
  - Three Men on a Horse, 1959, folder 6 (Box box 8)
  - Three Men on a Horse, 1973-1974, folder 7 (Box box 8)
  - The Threepenny Opera, 1963, folder 8 (Box box 8)
  - Three Penny Opera, 1968-1969, folder 9 (Box box 8)
  - Three Sisters, 1957, folder 10 (Box box 8)
  - Three Sisters, 1966, folder 11 (Box box 8)
  - Three Sisters, 1983-1984, folder 12 (Box box 8)
  - Tiger at the Gates, 1961, folder 13 (Box box 8)
  - Time of Your Life, 1962, folder 14 (Box box 8)
  - A Ragtime Revue, 1978-1979, folder 15 (Box box 8)
  - Tom, 1973-1974, folder 16 (Box box 8)
  - Tomfoolery, 1981-1982, folder 17 (Box box 8)
  - Tonight at 8:30, 1952, folder 18 (Box box 8)
  - Tot Family, 1975-1976, folder 19 (Box box 8)
  - Trikcs, 1971-1972, folder 20 (Box box 8)
  - Twelfth Night, 1951-1952, folder 21 (Box box 8)
  - Twelfth Night, 1971-1972, folder 22 (Box box 8)
  - Twelve Angry Men, 1963, folder 23 (Box box 8)
  - The Two Gentlemen of Verona, 1990-1991, folder 24 (Box box 8)
  - Uncle Vanya, 1963, folder 25 (Box box 8)
  - Under Milk Wood, 1962-1963, folder 26 (Box box 8)
  - Undiscovered Country, 1981-1982, folder 27 (Box box 8)
  - Uptight, 1971-1972, folder 28 (Box box 8)
  - The View from the Bridge, 1956, folder 29 (Box box 8)
  - Vivisections from the Blown Mind, 1990-1991, folder 30 (Box box 8)
  - Volpone, 1962, folder 31 (Box box 8)
  - Setphen Wade: Banjo Dancing, folder 32 (Box box 8)
  - Stephen Wade: On the Way Home, folder 33 (Box box 8)
  - Waiting for Godot, 1976, folder 34 (Box box 8)
  - A Walk in the Woods, 1988-1989, folder 35 (Box box 8)
  - The Wall, 1964, folder 36 (Box box 8)
  - Mr. Welh and Jessey Jim, 1964, folder 37 (Box box 8)
  - Restoration, 1985-1986, folder 1 (Box box 9)
  - Ring Round the Moon, 1960, folder 2 (Box box 9)
  - The Rivals, 1968, folder 3 (Box box 9)
  - Rivers and Ravines, 1988, folder 4 (Box box 9)
  - Rome and Juliet, 1958, folder 5 (Box box 9)
  - Room Service, 1954, folder 6 (Box box 9)
  - Room Service, 1968, folder 7 (Box box 9)
  - The Ruling Class, 1970-1971, folder 8 (Box box 9)
  - Stand-up Tragedy, 1989-1990, folder 9 (Box box 9)
  - Starting Here, Starting Now, 1977, folder 10 (Box box 9)
  - Status Quo Vadis, 1971-1972, folder 11 (Box box 9)
  - Still Life, 1982-1983, folder 12 (Box box 9)
  - Stray Dogs, 1985-1986, folder 13 (Box box 9)
  - A Streetcar Names Desire, 1977-1978, folder 14 (Box box 9)
  - The Suicide...a Comedy, 1981, folder 15 (Box box 9)
  - Summer of the 17th Doll, 1958, folder 15 (Box box 9)
  - The Tale of Lear, 1988-1989, folder 16 (Box box 9)
  - Tales from the Vienna Woods, 1978, folder 17 (Box box 9)
  - The Taming of the Shrew, 1950, folder 18 (Box box 9)
  - The Taming of the Shrew, 1984-1985, folder 19 (Box box 9)
  - Tartuffe, 1984-1985, folder 20 (Box box 9)
  - Tartuffe, 1954, folder 21 (Box box 9)
  - Wipe Out Games, 1970-1971, folder 22 (Box box 9)
  - Women and Water, 1985-1986, folder 23 (Box box 9)
  - Winter's Tale, 1979, folder 24 (Box box 9)
  - Weird in the Welleiron, 1966, folder 25 (Box box 9)
  - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf, 1974-1975, folder 26 (Box box 9)
  - What the Butler Saw, 1970-1971, folder 29 (Box box 9)
  - What Shall we Tell Caroline?, 1961-1962, folder 30 (Box box 9)
  - The Wild Duck, 1985-1986, folder 31 (Box box 9)
  - You Can't Take it With You, 1979-1980, folder 32 (Box box 9)
  - You Can't Take it With You, 1969-1970, folder 33 (Box box 9)
  - Woza Albert!, 1984-1985, folder 34 (Box box 9)
  - The World of Sholom Aleichem, 1955, folder 35 (Box box 9)
  - Zelman or the Madness of God, 1973-1974, folder 36 (Box box 9)
  - The Sing Ling Circus, 1962-1963, folder 1 (Box box 10)
  - Sizwe Banzi is Dead, The Island, 1974-1975, folder 2 (Box box 10)
  - Sic Characters in Search of an Author, 1988-1989, folder 3 (Box box 10)
  - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1968-1969, folder 4 (Box box 10)
  - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1961, folder 5 (Box box 10)
  - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1966, folder 6 (Box box 10)
  - Silent Night, Lonely Night, 1961, folder 7 (Box box 10)
  - The Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window, 1970-1971, folder 8 (Box box 10)
  - She Stoops to Conquer, 1990-1991, folder 9 (Box box 10)
  - She Stoops to Conquer, 1950-1951, folder 10 (Box box 10)
  - Shavings: An Evening of Short Shows, 1959, folder 11 (Box box 10)
  - Serjeant Musgraves's Dance, 1966, folder 12 (Box box 10)
  - The Seagull, 1990-1991, folder 13 (Box box 10)
  - Screenplay, 1982-1983, folder 14 (Box box 10)
  - The School for Wives, 1950-1951, folder 15 (Box box 10)
  - School for Wives, 1952, folder 16 (Box box 10)
  - Saturday, Sunday, Monday, 1976-1977, folder 17 (Box box 10)
  - Sevages Workshop, folder 18 (Box box 10)
  - The Scarecrow, 1950-1951, folder 19 (Box box 10)
  - Saint Joan, 1976, folder 20 (Box box 10)
  - Moon of the Yellow River, 1961-1962, folder 1 (Box box 11)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle, 1961-1962, folder 2 (Box box 11)
  - Madwoman of Chaillot, 1961, folder 3 (Box box 11)
  - Misc. 1961-1962, folder 4 (Box box 11)
  - Burning of the Topers, 1961-1962, folder 5 (Box box 11)
  - Uncle Verga, 1961-1962, folder 6 (Box box 11)
  - Time of Your Life, 1961-1962, folder 7 (Box box 11)
  - Once in a Lifetime, 1962-1963, folder 8 (Box box 11)
  - Under Milkwood, 1962-1963, folder 9 (Box box 11)
  - 12 Angry Men, 1962-1963, folder 10 (Box box 11)
  - Volpore, 1962-1963, folder 11 (Box box 11)
  - The Boilage, 1962-1963, folder 12 (Box box 11)
  - All The Way Home, 1962-1963, folder 13 (Box box 11)
  - Othello, 1962-1963, folder 14 (Box box 11)
  - Three Penny Opera, folder 15 (Box box 11)
  - Theatre Arts Magazine, April 1958, folder 16 (Box box 11)
  - The Carpenter magazine, March 1962, folder 17 (Box box 11)
  - Promenade Magazine at the Mayflower, November 1961, folder 18 (Box box 11)
  - National Business Woman, June 1963, folder 19 (Box box 11)
  - Newsweek, November 13, 1961, folder 20 (Box box 11)
  - The Sunday Star, September 17, 1961, folder 1 (Box box 12)
  - slides of Zelda Fichandler, March 1962, folder 2 (Box box 12)
  - slides; Chemmy Circle, folder 3 (Box box 12)
  - slides; 1968-1969 company, folder 4 (Box box 12)
  - Holiday Magazine, April 1962, folder 5 (Box box 12)
  - Alan Schneider photos, folder 6 (Box box 12)
  - misc. slides, folder 7 (Box box 12)
  - Russian tour photo negatives, folder 8 (Box box 12)
  - Russian tour slides and negatives, folder 9 (Box box 12)
  - 30th anniversary reel to reel and sheet music., folder 10 (Box box 12)
  - enlarged proofs of, Taming of the Shrew, The Affair and Hotel Paradiso, folder 11 (Box box 12)
  - enlarged photos, misc. productions, folder 12 (Box box 12)
  - blue prints of Arena Stage, folder 13 (Box box 12)
  - Misc. photos, folder 14 (Box box 12)
  - funny photos, folder 15 (Box box 12)
  - 60 misc. production shots, folder 16 (Box box 12)
  - photo of Zelda with President Ford, folder 17 (Box box 12)
  - misc. photos, folder 18 (Box box 12)
  - Negatives Roll #21074-3, folder 1 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives Roll #18371-3 Living Stage, folder 2 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives Roll #8659-2, folder 3 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll#8659-1 Living Stage, folder 4 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll#8313-4, folder 5 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll#8313-3, folder 6 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll#8313-2, folder 7 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #8313-1 Living Stage, folder 8 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #5496-5 Miller, folder 9 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #5496-1, folder 10 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #5496-3, folder 11 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #5496-2, folder 12 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #5496-1, folder 13 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1611-2, folder 14 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1611-1, folder 15 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1452-6, folder 16 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1452-5, folder 17 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1452-4, folder 18 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1452-3, folder 19 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1428-4, folder 20 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1452-2, folder 21 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1428-5, folder 22 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #1428-3, folder 23 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #21024-7, folder 24 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #210246, folder 25 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #21024-5, folder 26 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #21024-4, folder 27 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #21024-3, folder 28 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #21024-2, folder 29 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #21024-1, folder 30 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #10455-1, folder 31 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6716-1, folder 32 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6873-1, folder 33 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6755-4, folder 34 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6955-3, folder 35 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6955-2, folder 36 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6955-1, folder 37 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #5600-1, folder 38 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6715-4, folder 39 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6715-3, folder 40 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6715-2, folder 41 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #6715-1, folder 42 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #7146-4, folder 43 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #7146-3, folder 44 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #7146-2, folder 45 (Box box 13)
  - Negatives roll #7146-1, folder 46 (Box box 13)
  - Misc. negatives, loose envelops and individual negatives (Box box 14)
  - Women and Water, envelope 1 (Box box 15)
  - The Taming of the Shrew, envelope 2 (Box box 15)
  - Old Times, envelope 3 (Box box 15)
  - Happy End, envelope 4 (Box box 15)
  - As You Like It, envelope 5 (Box box 15)
  - Enrico IV, envelope 6 (Box box 15)
  - The Importance of being Ernest, envelope 7 (Box box 15)
  - Les Blancs, envelope 8 (Box box 15)
  - All the Kings Men, envelope 9 (Box box 15)
  - The Crucible, envelope 10 (Box box 15)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle, envelope 11 (Box box 15)
  - Light up the Sky, envelope 12 (Box box 15)
  - Heartbreak House, envelope 13 (Box box 15)
  - The Wild Duck, envelope 14 (Box box 15)
  - Piggy Bank, envelope 15 (Box box 15)
  - Is It Not Romantic, envelope 16 (Box box 15)
  - Crime and Punishment, envelope 17 (Box box 15)
  - Philadelphia Story, envelope 18 (Box box 15)
  - Joe Turner, envelope 19 (Box box 15)
  - Measure for Measure, folder 20 (Box box 15)
  - Fences, envelope 21 (Box box 15)